# Premkamon Boonked

UX/UI Creative Design Specialist

premkamon.work@gmail.com https://yokpkm.web.app 084-297-4414 I work as UX/UI designer with over 4 years of experience. Skilled in UI design for application and responsive website, design system, UX research and UI development. Now, I'm looking for a role that I can enhance my skills to design outstanding user experiences.

## **EDUCATION**

Bangkok, Thailand

King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

Bachelor Degree in Science Second-Class Honors 2016 - 2020

#### **SKILLES**

UI Design

Design System

UX Research

UX Writing

Wireframe / Prototype

React Typescript

CSS / HTML

## **TOOLS**

Figma

Adobe XD

Visual Studio Code

#### **EXPERIENCES**

## UX/UI Creative Design Specialist

Orbix Trade Co., Ltd | 2022 - Present

- Designed the UI for mobile application and website from requirement that under legal regulator
- Researched to improve the product with consistent and simply user experience
- Collaborated with other teams, including product owner, business analyst, developer and QA

## UX/UI Designer

Future Makers Co., Ltd | 2020 - 2022

- Designed the responsive website and application from user requirements
- Developed the UI that design by myself. Skilled in React Typescript, React Native and Next.js

## Intern UX Designer

Refinn International Dot Com Co., Ltd | 2018

- Researched and interviewed to collected the pain point
- Designed wireframe and prototype